# Subhan Ahmed

## Front-end & Web Developer

Hello, I am Subhan Ahmed, currently pursuing my Bachelor's degree and in my 2nd year. I have also completed a web development course in 2022. As a front-end and web developer, I aim to leverage my skills in designing modern and mobile-responsive websites. I am to create effective and visually appealing web solutions that enhance your business with my creativity and technical expertise



developersubhanahmed@gmail.



0334-3760625



karachi, pakistan



linkedin.com/in/subhanahmed1



github.com/subhanrizwan

## **EDUCATION**

#### **BS Computer Science**

Sindh Madressatul Islam University

2023 - Present Karachi, Pakistan

#### Intermediate

Govt Science IslamiaCollege

2021 - 2022 Karachi, Pakistan

#### Matric

Aasa Jalal Secondary School

2019 - 2020 Karachi, Pakistan

# **SKILLS**

JavaScript

React js ui

Html5

Css3

Java

wordpress

Assembly

C basic

Bootstrap

Ant design

Firebase

MySQL

Github

PhotoShop

#### **EXPERIENCE**

# Web Developer Internship Coders Cave

06/2024 - 07/2024

- Developed and contributed to various web development projects, gaining hands-on experience in clear front-end and back-end technologies.
- Worked on designing and implementing responsive user interfaces using HTML5, CSS3, and Bootstrap
- Integrated Firebase for database management and user authentication.
- Languages & Technologies: HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, ES6, Firebase, Bootstrap

# Frontend Developer

A Bit Much Co

09/2024 - Present

# Private Teaching

8 & 9 Class

2022 - 2023 Karachi, Pakistan

# **LANGUAGES**

#### Urdu

Full Professional Proficiency

#### English

Limited Working Proficiency

#### CERTIFICATES

#### Web Development Internship (Coders cave)

https://subhanrizwan.github.io/Certificate-coders-cave/

Hafiz e Quran (01/2013 - 01/2016)

The document I received was from the Department of Augaf, Sindh, in 2016.

# **SOFT SKILLS**

Problem-Solving

Time Management

Teamwork

# **PERSONAL PROJECTS**

#### Chat Web App

 $\hbox{$\blacksquare$ https://subhanrizwan.github.io/Golden-chat-app-project}$ 

#### Weather App

□ https://subhanrizwan.github.io/Normal-Weather-app-project/

#### My Portfolio (React Js)

https://subhan-pfolio-react.netlify.app/

## Turo Clone (React Js)

https://subhan-react-turoapp.netlify.app/

# Quiz Application (Html, Css, Js)

https://subhan-quizapp.netlify.app